affiliatewindow.com 2011-11-10

# 1

Digital Window Limited ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your
privacy.
This      policy    (together      with    our     Terms       of   Website       Use)
http://www.affiliatewindow.com/documents/legal/terms_of_use.pdf           and      any
other documents referred to in it) sets out the basis on which any personal data
we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please
read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your
personal data and how we will treat it.
For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), the data controller
is Digital Window Limited of 3rd Floor, 100 Leman Street, London E1 8EU.
Our nominated representative for the purpose of the Act is Peter Loveday.
1       Information we may collect from you
        We may collect and process the following data about you:
1.1     Information that you provide by filling in forms on any of our websites
        which      shall     include     without      limitation    the      following
        www.affiliatewindow.com        and   http://www.shopwindow.com           (“the
        Websites”). This includes information provided at the time of registering
        to use the Website(s), subscribing to our service, posting material or
        requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when
        you report a problem with the Website(s).
1.2     If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
1.3     We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research
        purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
1.4     Details of transactions you carry out through the Website(s) and of the
        fulfilment of your orders.
1.5     Details of your visits to the Website(s) including, but not limited to, traffic
        data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this
        is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources
        that you access.
2       IP addresses and cookies
2.1     We may collect information about your computer, including where
        available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system
        administration. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions
        and patterns, and does not identify any individual.
2.2     For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general
        internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of
                                           1

    your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your
    computer's hard drive. They help us to improve the Website(s) and to
    deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us to:
    (a)     estimate our audience size and usage pattern;
    (b)     store information about your preferences, and so allow us to
            customise the Website(s) according to your individual interests;
    (c)     speed up your searches; and
    (d)     recognise you when you return to the Website(s).
2.3 You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your
    internet browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies.
    However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain
    parts of the Website(s). Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so
    that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to
    the Website(s).
2.4 Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have
    no control.
3   Where we store your personal data
3.1 The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and be stored at,
    a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be
    processed by staff operating outside the EEA who may work for us or for
    one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things
    the processing of your payment details and the provision of support
    services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer,
    storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to
    ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this
    privacy policy.
3.2 Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which
    enables you to access certain parts of the Website(s), you are responsible
    for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a
    password with anyone.
3.3 Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not
    completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal
    data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the
    Website(s); any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received
    your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try
    to prevent unauthorised access.
4   Uses made of the information
4.1 We use information held about you in the following ways:
                                        2

    (a)     to ensure that content from the Website(s) is presented in the most
            effective manner for you and for your computer.
    (b)     to provide you with information, products or services that you
            request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have
            consented to be contacted for such purposes.
    (c)     to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into
            between you and us.
    (d)     to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service,
            when you choose to do so.
    (e)     to notify you about changes to our service.
4.2 We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your
    data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may
    be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post
    or telephone.
4.3 If you have purchased goods or services from the Website(s), we will only
    contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about
    goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous
    sale to you.
4.4 If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to
    use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if
    you have consented to this.
4.5 If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details
    on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box
    situated on the form on which we collect your data.
5   Disclosure of your information
5.1 We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group,
    which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its
    subsidiaries from time to time, as defined in section 736 of the UK
    Companies Act 1985 or section 1519 of the UK Companies Act 2006 as
    applicable.
5.2 We may disclose your personal information to third parties:
    (a)     In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which
            case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller
            or buyer of such business or assets.
    (b)     If Digital Window Limited or substantially all of its assets are
            acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it
            about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
                                       3

       If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to
       comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms
       of                               Website                                  Use
       http://www.affiliatewindow.com/documents/legal/terms_of_use.pdf and or
       any other agreements between you and us, or to protect the rights,
       property, or safety of Digital Window Limited, our customers, or others.
       This includes exchanging information with other companies and
       organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk
       reduction.
6      Your rights
6.1    You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for
       marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your
       data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to
       disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can
       exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes
       on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right
       at any time by contacting us at Digital Window Ltd of the 3rd Floor, 100
       Leman Street, London, E1 8EU or email chris@affiliatewindow.com
6.2    Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of
       our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any
       of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy
       policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these
       policies or for any of the personal data which may be collected from you
       under these policies by such third parties. Please check these policies
       before you submit any personal data to these websites.
7      Access to information
       The Act gives you the right to access personal information held about you
       by us. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act.
       Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 (or any other fee
       determined by law) to meet our costs in providing you with details of the
       information we hold about you.
8      Changes to our privacy policy
       Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be
       posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. If
       use of the data changes we will have to get consent anyway regardless of
       what we put in the privacy policy.
9      Contact
       Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are
       welcomed and should be addressed to Digital Window Ltd of the 3rd Floor,
       100 Leman Street, London, E1 8EU or email chris@affiliatewindow.com.
Issue Date: 31th May 2011
                                         4
